Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Journal of Drug Issues - Part 2 (Duplicate), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Copy of the pages in folder 9
- Journal of Industrial Relations, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Volume contains a review of a book by Harrison Trice
- Key Issues - Strategies for Employee Assistance Programs (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Lessons from EAPs for Drug Screening, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Linking Organizational and Occupational Theory Through the Concept of Culture (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Linking Organizational and Occupational Theory Through the Concept of Culture (Alternate Version) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Alternate Version of the article in folder 14
- Management of Ineffective Performance, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Management Styles, Perceptions of Substance Abuse, and Employee Assistance Programs in Organizations, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Managerial Commitment - A Multivariate and Path Analytic Approach, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Managerial Commitment - A Multivariate and Path Analytic Approach (Duplicate), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Copy of the article in folder 18
- Managerial Ideologies and Organizational Control - How Effective is Discipline?, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Managerial Ideologies and Organizational Control - how Effective is Discipline? (Duplicate), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  Copy of the article in folder 20
- Managerial Ideologies and the Use of Discipline, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Managerial Receptivity and Implementation of Policies, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Managing Corporate Cultures Through Rites and Ceremonials, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Managing Corporate Cultures Through Rites and Ceremonials (Duplicate), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Measuring and Predicting Managerial Success, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Mental Health and White Collar Urbanites - Psychiatric Impairments Among New York City Clerical Workers, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Mental Health in Work Organizations - A Re-Examination, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Methodological Issues in Worksite Research, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Methodology for Evaluating Conference Leadership Training, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Metropolitan State College Employee Assistance Program, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Models of Workplace Risk Factors and Drinking Behavior, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- A Multiple Factor Approach to Schizophrenia and Social Class, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Musings of a Devoted Outsider, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- The Myth of the Troubled Supervisor, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- The Myth of the Troubled Supervisor (Duplicate), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Narcotics Anonymous, 1986-1992 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Neglected Aspect of the Managerial Role - Predicting Managers' Use of Discipline, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Neglected Aspect of the Managerial Role - Predicting Managers' Use of Discipline (Duplicate), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  Copy of the article in folder 38
- New Light on Identifying the Alcoholic Employee, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- The Night Watchmen - A Study of an Isolated Occupation, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Normalization - A Neglected Complement to Labeling Theory, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Observations on the Cost to Industry and Business by Drug Using Employees (Box 14, Folder 43)
- An Occupation in Conflict, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Occupational Risk Factors in Mental Health and the Impact of Role Change Experience, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Occupational Risk Factors in Mental Health and the Impact of Role Change Experience, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  Copy of the article in folder 45
- Occupational Role Change and Mental Health, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Occupational Stress Cases (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Occupational Subcultures (Box 14, Folder 49)
- On the Construction of Drinking Norms in Work Organizations, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- On the Construction of Drinking Norms in Work Organizations (Manuscript), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  Manuscript copy of the article in folder 50
- On Judging Implements Available for Executing a Job-Based Alcoholism Policy (Box 14, Folder 52)
- On Judging Implements Available for Executing a Job-Based Alcoholism Policy (Duplicate) (Box 14, Folder 53)
- On the Problem of Clarifying Commitment Theory, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Organizational and Occupational Dimensions of EAPs, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Organizational Structure and the Implementation of Change Within Federal Sector Organizations, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Organizations and Social Problems, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Organizations and Types of Occupational Communities, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Organizations and Types of Occupational Communities (Duplicate), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  Copy of the article in folder 58
- Outsider Role in Field Study, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Passing Organizational Cultures onto Newcomers (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Socialization Tactics, Self-Efficacy, and Newcomers' Adjustments to Organizations, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Penetration Rates, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Penetration Rates (Duplicate), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Personnel Appraisal and Job Descriptions in Extension Supervision, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- The Personnel Manager and His Self-Image, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Perspectives on Job-Based Programs for Alcohol and Drug Problems Part I, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Predicting How Federal Managers Perceive Criteria Used for Promotion, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Preperformance Testing (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Present Day Approaches to Alcohol and Alcoholism, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- The Problem Drinker in Industry, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Prevention of Deviant Behavior, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Prevention of Deviant Behavior (Duplicate), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  Copy of the article in folder 72
- Prevention of Deviant Behavior (Second Duplicate), 1970 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  Copy of the article in both folder 72 and folder 73
- The Problem Drinker on the Job, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- The Problem Drinker on the Job (Duplicate), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  Earlier printing of the article in folder 75
- Problem Drinking and Alcoholism, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Program Adoption and Management Beliefs (Box 14, Folder 78)
- A Proposed Study of Socio-Cultural Changes Among Alcoholics Entering Alcoholics Anonymous (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Psychiatric Impairment Among "Middle Americans", 1972 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Psychological Adaptation to Occupational Role Change (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Published Summaries - Part I, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Published Summaries - Part II, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- A Rank Order Analysis of the Symptoms of Alcoholism, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- A Rank Order Analysis of the Symptoms of Alcoholism (Duplicate), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Reaching the Impaired Professional, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Reaction of Supervisors to Emotionally Disturbed Employees - A Study of Deviation in a Work Environment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- A Reexamination of the Relation Between Size and Various Components of Organizational Complexity, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- References (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Relationship between Primary and Secondary Deviation, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Report of the Evaluation of the New York State Division of Alcoholism, Occupational Alcoholism Expansion Grant and State-Wide Occupational System, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- A Retrospective Study of Similarities and Differences between Men and Women Employees, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- A Retrospective Study of Similarities and Differences between Men and Women Employees (Duplicate), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Report on Alcoholism in the State of Maryland, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- "Research" Lecture - North American Congress, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Resolving Role Conflict - A Test and an Addition (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Rites and Ceremonials in Organizational Cultures, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Rites and Ceremonials in Organizational Cultures (Duplicate), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Copy of the article in folder 16
- Rites of Passage in Work Careers, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Rites of Passage in Work Careers (Duplicate), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Roadblocks in Employee Programs, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Role of Ceremonials in Organizational Behavior, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- The Role, Concerns, and Needs of Supervisors in Occupational Alcoholism Programs (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Role of the Labor Union in Com[any Based Alcohol Programs, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- The Role of the Union in Industrial Alcoholism Programs, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Routinization of Change - Implementation of Policy in Federal Organizations, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Rural-Reared Workers and Labor Turnover, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Sandhogs - Light at the End of the Tunnel, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Schizophrenia and the Poor, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Schizophrenia and the Social Structure, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- A Selection Approach to the Improvement of Treatment for Alcoholics (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Selection for Treatment - A Predictive Evaluation of an Alcoholism Treatment Program, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- A Selective Approach to Treatment, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- The Self Reaction - A Neglected Dimension of "Labeling Theory", 1969 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Self-Reaction to an Occupational Program (Box 15, Folder 34)
- The Sick Role, Labeling Theory, and the Deviant Drinker, 1968-1982 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Social Construction of Alcohol Problems in a Union's Peer Counseling Program, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Social Construction of Alcohol Problems in a Union's Peer Counseling Program (Published Version), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  Published version of the article in folder 36
- Social Organization and Alcoholism - A Review of Significant Research since 1940, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Social Organization and Culture of a Club for Former Mental Patients, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Social Control in Worksettings, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Social Control in Worksettings (Duplicate), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- A Sociocultural History of Alcoholics Anonymous (Box 15, Folder 42)
- A Sociocultural History of Alcoholics Anonymous (Published Version), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  Published version of the article in folder 42
- A Sociocultural History of Alcoholics Anonymous (Duplicate), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  Copy of the article in folder 43
- Sociological Factors in Association with Alcoholics Anonymous, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Sociological Perspectives on Community Mental Health (Box 15, Folder 46)
- A Sociological Property of Drugs, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Sociopsychological Predictors of Affiliation with Alcoholics Anonymous - A Longitudinal Study of "Treatment Success", 1970 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Soft Drugs, the Campus, and You, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Some Notes on Evaluating Existing Programs, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Some Observations on Research Utilization of Research Data in the Occupational Alcoholism Programming Field, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Sowing Seeds of Change - How Work Organizations in New York State Responded to Occupational Program Consultants, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Sowing Seeds of Change - How Work Organizations in New York State Responded to Occupational Program Consultants (Duplicate), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Strategy of Constructive Confrontation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Strategies of Preventive Psychiatry - The Case of Alcoholism Prevention, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Stress on the Job, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Study of Alcoholism Policy (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Study of Effectiveness of Railroad Alcohol Programs, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Study of the Occupational Self-Image of Personnel Managers (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Study of the Process of Affiliation with Alcoholics Anonymous, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Study of Union-Management Cooperation in a Long-Standing Alcoholism Program, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Study of Union-Management Cooperation in a Long-Standing Alcoholism Program (Published Version), 1984 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  Published Version of the article in folder 61
- Studying Organizational Cultures Through Rites and Ceremonials, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Studying Organizational Cultures Through Rites and Ceremonials (Manuscript), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  Manuscript version of the article in folder 63
- Studying Troubled Employees - Gaining and Keeping Research Access, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Studying Troubled Employees - Gaining and Keeping Research Access (Duplicate), 1984 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  Copy of the article in folder 65
- Subcultural Approach to Organizational Cultures, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Summary of Impressions from Occupational Conference Mental Health Conference at White Plains (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Summary of Recent Studies Done by the Program on Alcoholism and Occupational Health, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- The Supervisor - Key Player in EAPs, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Supervisory Training about Alcoholics and Other Problem Employees (Box 15, Folder 71)
- Teaching About Organizational Cultures - The Field Format, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 72)
- Teaching About Organizational Cultures - The Field Format (Duplicate), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  Copy of the article from folder 72
- Testimony Before Subcommittee on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, Senate Committee on Human Resources, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 74)
- Top MGM = Selling Them, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 75)
- Top MGM = Selling Them continued (Box 15, Folder 76)
- Training as a Change Agent, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- Treatment and Rehabilitation, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Treatment, Types, Self-Help, and Anonymous Groups, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Trouble and Emotional Health Problems, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- The Troubled Employee (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The Troubled Employee (Duplicate) (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Troubled Supervisors (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Truth and Fiction in Occupational Stories - The Case of the Troubled Supervisor (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Truth and Fiction in Occupational Stories - The Case of the Troubled Supervisor (Published Version), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Published version of the article in folder 7
- Twelve Steps, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Unanticipated Returns of Training, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Understanding EAP Self-Referral, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Unidentified Paper (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Use of Application Blank Data, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Using Six Organizational Rites to Change Culture, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Using Six Organizational Rites to Change Culture (Duplicate), 1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Utilization Process (Box 16, Folder 16)
- The Utilization Process - A Conceptual Framework and Synthesis of Empirical Findings, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- The Weighted Application Blank, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- What is an EAP - The Place of Qualitative and Quantitative Research in Understanding Programs (Box 16, Folder 19)
- What We Know about Alcoholism in Industry, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Why the Experts Say Alcoholics Anonymous Still is Drinker's Pal, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Reprint of a newspaper article
- Women, Alcohol, and Drugs, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Women Employees and Job-Based Alcoholism Programs, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Work Accidents and the Problem Drinker, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Work Related Risk Factors, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Work-Related Outcomes, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Workmen's Compensation and the Emotionally Disturbed Employee, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Workplace Risk Factors and Drinking Behavior, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- The Workplace as Locale for Risks and Interventions in Alcohol Abuse, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- The Workplace as Locale for Risks and Interventions in Alcohol Abuse (Duplicate), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Workplace Safety - Preperformance Testing vs. Drug Testing (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Yale Summer School Lectures (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Yale Summer School Lectures continued (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous (The Book of Tax Knowledge), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous (Letter to Lt. General Moore), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous (The Green Book), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous (Handwritten Notes) (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous Untitled Part I (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Untitled Part II (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Untitled Part III (Box 16, Folder 40)
- An Organizational Critique of Evaluation Research - Hardin - 1 of 4, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- An Organizational Critique of Evaluation Research - Hardin - 2 of 4, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- An Organizational Critique of Evaluation Research - Hardin - 3 of 4, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- An Organizational Critique of Evaluation Research - Hardin - 4 of 4, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Publication Lists, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Book Reviews by Trice, 1958-1987 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Book Reviews about Trice Writings, 1967-1990 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Correspondence Part I, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Correspondence Part II, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Correspondence Part III, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Part IV, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Part V, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Part VI, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Research Plan/Grant Application, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Research Plans/Grant Information, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Research Plans - Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Research Plans - Manufacturing (Duplicate), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Copy of the notes in folder 9
- Research Plans - Installation, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Research Plans - Service Centers, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Research Plans/ Grant Information - Western Electric, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Research Plans/ Grant Information - Evaluating Jobs-Based Programs for Problem Drinkers, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Includes Harrison Trice's Social Security Number
- Research Plans - A Study of Alcoholism Policy (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Arrangements - Location Contacts (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Research Plans - Personnel Information Summary, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- General Data (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Composite Data (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Preliminary Results, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- General Results - Graphs - Part I (Box 17, Folder 21)
- General Results - Graphs - Part II (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Integrated Responses (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Working Reports (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Working Report #1, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Working Report #2, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Working Report #3, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Working Report #4 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Working Report #4 (Duplicate) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Copy of the report in folder 28
- Working Report #5, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Working Report #6, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Working Report #6 (Duplicate), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  Copy of the report in folder 31
- Working Reports 7 and 8, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Working Reports 9 and 10, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Working Report #11, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Working Reports #12-#16, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Working Reports #17-#19, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Working Reports #20-#23, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Working Report #25, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Working Reports #30-#35, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Working Reports #36-#41, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Working Report #42, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Working Report #43, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Working Report #44, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Working Report #45, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Working Report #46, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Working Report #47, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Working Report #48, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Working Report #49, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Working Report #49a, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Working Report #50, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Working Report #51, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Working Report #52, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Working Report #53, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Working Report #54, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Working Report #55, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Working Report #56, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Working Report #57, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Working Report #58, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Miscellaneous Notes from Western Electric Study (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Frequencies and Data on Medical Variables, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- "A" Form Miscellaneous Information (Box 17, Folder 62)
- "B" Form Miscellaneous Information (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Tables (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Data and Analyses (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Coding Instructions and Information, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Coding Instructions, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Miscellaneous Survey Data, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Membership Information Summary Forms, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Membership Information Summary Forms and Info, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Personnel Information Summary (PIS) Forms, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- PIS Forms and Data, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Data 1, 1974-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Data 2, 1969-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Data 3, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Data 4, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Codebook for Western Electric Corporate Records (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Codebook for Form A Supervisors (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Form A Codebook, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Form A Codebook (Duplicate), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 7
- Form A Codebook (Second Duplicate), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Copy of the codebook in both folder 7 and folder 8
- Form B Supervisors Codebook (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Form B Codebook (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Form B Codebook (Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 11
- Form B Coding Info, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- General Manager Codebook (Box 18, Folder 14)
- General Manager Codebook (Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 14
- General Manager Codebook (Second Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Copy of the codebook in both folder 14 and folder 15
- Medical Director Codebook (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Medical Director Codebook (Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 17
- Medical Director Codebook (Second Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Copy of the codebook in both folder 17 and folder 18
- Medical Director Codebook (Third Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 17, 18, and 19
- Staff Advisor's Codebook, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Staff Advisor's Codebook (Duplicate), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 21
- Staff Advisor's Codebook (Second Duplicate, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  Copy of the codebook in both folder 21 and folder 22
- Staff Advisor's Codebook (Third Duplicate), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Copy of the codebook in folders 21, 22, and 23
- Union Official's Codebook (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Union Official's Codebook (Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Copy of the codebook in folder 25
- Union Official's Codebook (Second Duplicate) (Box 18, Folder 27)
  Copy of the codebook in both folder 25 and folder 26
- Union Official's Codebook and Additional Coding Information, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- EAP Interview Form, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- "A" Interview Forms, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- "A" Interview Forms (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Copy of the form in folder 30
- "A" Interview Forms (Earlier Version), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  Earlier version of the form in both folder 30 and folder 31
- "B" Interview Forms, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- "B" Interview Forms (Duplicate), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  Copy of the form in folder 33
- "B" Interview Forms (Second Duplicate), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Copy of the form in both folder 33 and folder 34
- General Manager Interview Form, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- General Manager Interview Form (Earlier Version), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  Earlier version of the form in folder 36
- Medical Director Interview Forms, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 38)